### Hubungi

mikram216@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-ikram216 (LinkedIn)

### Keahlian Teratas

React Native
Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel

# Muhammad Ikram

Fullstack Developer | Node JS | Express JS | React JS | React Native

Banda Aceh, Nanggroe Aceh Darussalam, Indonesia

## Ringkasan

I have experience as a Fullstack Web Developer, having completed a 3-month training program on Fazztrack. My interest in programming began when I started studying Javascript. I have created several project websites using Node.js and Express.js for the Backend and React.js and Next.js for the Frontend, with PostgreSQL and Supabase as databases. Additionally, I am familiar with working on Github.

I am capable of communicating and collaborating within a team, as well as working independently.

Besides English, I also speak Arabic.

### Pengalaman

**Fazztrack** 

Fullstack Developer Talent September 2022 - Januari 2023 (5 bulan)

Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

As a Fazztrack Academy Talent, I built my own projects using React JS for web applications and React Native for mobile applications. In addition, I collaborated with my team to build a website application using React JS and Next JS.

Nurul Iman Senior High School

2 tahun 5 bulan

Staff and Administration

Agustus 2021 - Desember 2021 (5 bulan)

Kota Administrasi Jakarta Timur, Jakarta, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

I have experience in assisting with recapitulation data and administration tasks for schools and students. I am proficient in working with Microsoft Office, which allows me to efficiently handle tasks such as data entry, organizing records, and creating reports.

Arabic Teacher

#### Agustus 2019 - Desember 2021 (2 tahun 5 bulan)

Kota Administrasi Jakarta Timur, Jakarta, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

I had the privilege of teaching Arabic language at Nurul Iman Senior High School. As their language instructor, I focused on improving their skills in speaking, writing, listening, and reading. It was a fulfilling experience to see my students progress and become more confident in their language abilities..

### Pendidikan

#### Fazztrack

Talent , Fullstack Developer · (September 2022)

#### Universitas Terbuka

Sistem Informasi · (Juli 2022)

Lembaga Ilmu Pengetahuan Islam dan Arab ( LIPIA )

D-2, Bahasa dan Sastra Arab · (September 2016 - Juli 2018)